Welcome back, Aika.
Ultranate?! But that's impossible!
All orbital attack satellites have been destroyed, sir.
Excellent. We can proceed to stage three of the operation.
Aye, sir.
Proceeding to stage three.
Raggu energy, switch to line A!
Open transmission antennas!
Transmission antennas, open!
Adjusting angles. Unit 1, plus 0.8 Unit 2...
Just what are you trying to do?
Do you want to know?
Final adjustment, complete.
Right. Mr. Hargen?
Commence transmission of Raggu energy.
Now you're completely part of me, I don't want to hold back anymore
I remember, we got GD
If curiosity moves in the point of the compass
Then most likely the special power will arise
Silent city, we're salvager
I will one day find the skyscraper of the submerged city
Don't be afraid, come together
By passing through time, let's revive
All the things that the sun shines upon
I miss you
I want to convey it to you, I don't want you to forget
I take you
Since there is a world awaiting that no one has ever seen
Let it go
Always
A Flower Blooming in Space
Now, then, will you please hand over the data disc?
We don't have time to be talking about that!
Aren't you going to do anything about that battleship of his?!
The military has thrown together a space battle fleet
that's preparing to scramble to destroy the battleship.
Destroy?!
Then you're going to leave Aika and Rion to die, just like that?!
I don't recall guaranteeing your lives on this mission.
What did you say?!
Wait!
Please, give us a chance! You have to!
I'll take care of that ship even if it kills me!
So, please! Give us one more chance!
Raggu is normally located at various points deep within the Earth.
It moves freely, carried in the mantle's convection currents.
The great disaster that occurred years ago happened when,
by accident, a great deal of Raggu surfaced simultaneously.
My plan is to beam Raggu energy down from orbit,
and cause the Raggu in the Earth to all simultaneously surface.
In short, my aim is to artificially create an earthquake,
hundreds of times more powerful than the one that struck twenty years ago.
But, if you do that...
The civilization of those foolish apes
shall return to nothingness in a very short time.
Along with the apes themselves, of course.
lf... If you do that, you won't survive either!
The environment wouldn't support human life after that, you know!
You have nothing to fear. The environment will be regenerated.
That is the whole aim of this project, you see.
To regenerate?
Yes. That's why this ship also carries the DNA sets
of several thousand species of animals and plants.
The earth and seas shall be reconstructed.
A new ecosystem will form.
And then we shall descend to the new Earth.
We shall build an ideal human civilization. A Utopia!
Utopia?
Does that explain...
As you've guessed by now, the ones who will build this new Utopia
shall be me and the women with me aboard this ship!
By the way, Miss...
How about it?
Would you be interested in passing my genes to a new generation?
Absolutely not!
What is with you?! No matter how you say it,
all you're after is to create a harem you can have all to yourself!
Take her away!
Sir!
Why, you... You can't make me do what you want!
You gold-buttoned girly man!
You curly-haired pervert!
And where'd you get that stupid uniform?! Group Sounds? Julie?!
I'm going to have to pay you back for last time!
I've gotta do something. I've gotta do something.
I've gotta warn Papa and Aika somehow.
Shut up! Don't talk, just walk!
Okay, now stay here and keep quiet.
Rion! Rion, is that you?!
But why are you wearing... Oh, no. Come on...
Rion, are you all right? Rion! Rion, wake up!
I can hear Aika's voice...
Aika! Aika, is that really you?
That's right. Rion, I'm sorry I took so long.
I'm so happy. I can't believe you really came back for me.
What do you mean? Of course I did!
You're my precious partner, aren't you?
Forgive me. If I hadn't messed up,
this wouldn't have happened to you.
No! Don't say that! Don't say that!
I'm just so happy that you came back for me!
Rion...
Aika!
Aika, your arm!
It's all right. Just a little scraped, that's all.
You mean...
Now that I've found you in one piece,
let's get out of here, as fast as possible!
So, that's what Hargen is up to.
Yeah, unless we do something, Earth's in big trouble.
That's why I...
Yes, but first,
we have to concentrate on escaping from this ship.
Okay? Follow me, and stay close.
But... Aika!
Sorry.
Where's the escape pod?! Show us!
Miss Neina!
What is she?! A cyborg?
Aika!
Rion!
I see that you've really got some guts, don't you?
Aika!
Hey, you! What are you doing to Aika?!
Aren't you going to ask for help? What's wrong, hm?
What?!
No way... Aika...
Rion, if I could have, I never would've let you see me like this.
I'm sorry for hiding this until now.
It's... It's...
Cool! That is just so totally cool! Aika!
Too cool! So, how do you transform?! You lucky stiff!
It's wonderful! Like something out of an anime!
Hey.
Why didn't you ever tell me about something this great?
People can be so mean! Even you, Aika.
Um, well...
So, how does it work?
Hey! Quit ignoring me!
Small craft rapidly approaching, sir!
What?
I'm not sure, but I think it's a national space force vessel.
Orders, sir?
We've no time to waste. Draw it in, then destroy it with one shot.
Strange. They must have noticed us, but they're doing nothing.
Look sharp, Bandra!
Right.
Craft has collided with antenna #3, checking damage now!
Antenna heavily damaged! Nonfunctional!
Transmission output down by 25%!
What?!
Compensate the output loss with the remaining three antennas!
But, sir! That'll put much too high a load on them!
It's all right! It'll still be within their specifications!
All right! We'll transfer inside there, now.
Bandra, take us over to the nearest hatch!
Gotcha!
The vessel has docked with us! Hatch #7!
Get an armed squad down there!
Aye, aye!
Hey, cut it out! I said cut it out!
What's the big idea, huh?
You were in the way, dammit! Quit daydreaming, will ya!
What do you think you're doing, forcing me to come with you?!
Hey! Are you listening to me?!
Here!
Watch your back!
Right.
Gusto, you better hurry!
Okay!
You jerk...
Gusto, you handle setting the explosive charges.
I'll look for Rion and Aika!
Sure! Later!
Sorry, but would you show me the way, Miss Meipia?
Yeah, yeah. I'll show you. Right this way.
For crying out loud...
Come on, let's use this chance to get to the escape pods!
You won't get away!
Reprogramming, complete.
Antenna load is still within the maximum spec. It's working.
Schedule loss?
At most, 13% behind.
Excellent.
Mr. Hargen?
Now what's the matter?
Fighting has just broken out in Area 58, sir.
The report is that there's been considerable damage.
Route the video over here.
What?!
Show me the surveillance from the lab section room!
Lab section room, on screen.
When did...
Carry on with the plan!
Aye, sir!
Are they here?
No! Are they here?
No!
All right, you guys head for Area 69.
Aye, aye!
There! Huh? What the hell?
What?
What's wrong? Have you found them?
Well, yeah, I've found them, but...
What the hell is going on here?
You know where it is?
Yeah.
All right, let's go!
Freeze!
All right, put your hands up!
It can't be!
Why? My Ultranate is supposed to be greatly superior to yours.
But then why?
Why is yours better than mine?
I won't accept it! I absolutely will not accept it!
What...
Her human body can't take the effects of Ultranate any longer.
Normally, the fusion of Ultranate and a human is extremely dangerous.
It doesn't matter how strong a mind or body they may have,
sudden fusion always destroys the human host eventually.
Help me, big brother!
Can't we do anything for her?
Unfortunately, there's nothing we can do.
That is so gross!
Rion, let's go!
Right.
Rion... Rion!
So you can already repel the force of this gun.
The adaptability of Ultranate metal is greater than I expected.
Ultranate metal...
Before the Great Disaster, researchers were working on
a fluid metal life form to enhance physical strength intensively.
Normally, it could take the form of a piece of clothing.
When activated, it would then spread over the body,
to a thickness of only a few microns,
providing armor protection and speed and strength magnification.
If it had been successful,
it would have been a new era in the art of weapons design.
But its development was very difficult.
Most test subjects lost their lives,
and the project was thought to be a failure.
There were reports of a single success with a young girl.
Unfortunately, it was thought that she and the data on her
were lost after the disaster occurred.
That young girl, Miss Aika... It was you, wasn't it?
Unfortunately, I won't be able to use Neina anymore.
So, now, Miss Aika, I'll make you work for me in her place!
You still have that much strength left?
For Aika's sake, you must be destroyed!
No! Stop it! Stop!
I'm still so immature at heart.
Raggu resonance, confirmed.
Mr. Hargen, we've confirmed Raggu resonance.
Understood. I'll be back in a little while.
Miss Aika, this time I'll make you mine.
An explosion?!
We've had explosions on the antenna joint
and throughout the ship! It must be sabotage!
Hurry! This way!
Now what?!
I've got you, big brother.
Neina...
Now you'll be mine and mine alone, won't you?
Let me go, Neina.
Oh, no. I'll never let you go now.
Let me go, Neina!
No, no! If I do, you'll just run off somewhere!
I won't do it!
Don't be silly! I won't go anywhere.
I'm always there by your side, aren't I?
You liar!
Oh, big brother, now you can always care for me.
Always love me.
You see, it's because I love you so much!
No! Stop it! Please, Neina, stop!
The Raggu energy is reversing! The main cable has burned through!
Close all connections to the Raggu reactor!
Switch back to standard power!
Locking out all reactor connection circuits.
It's no use! I can't lock them out!
The energy in the reactor is backflowing!
Big brother? What's wrong? Do you hate me now, big brother?
Aren't you supposed to love your little sister?
Rion! Rion!
We've lost the transmitters!
No! I won't do it! Big brother is mine alone!
I won't... I won't give him to anyone!
Aika!
Back on active duty, sir?
Yeah, I am! Somebody forced me into it!
Big brother... Big brother... Big brother... Big brother...
Mr. Hargen! Mr. Hargen, please respond!
It's no use! There's no response from Mr. Hargen!
Captain, the Raggu reactor is out of control.
It'll destroy the ship!
Raggu resonance has been completely lost.
The operation has failed!
Captain...
All hands, abandon ship!
Aye!
Hurry! Get to the escape capsules!
Get going! You can still run!
Right!
All gunnery personnel have evacuated!
Captain!
Let's go.
What are you waiting for?! Come on, this is a short cut!
I'm running as fast as I can, you know!
What does Rion eat to make her so heavy?!
You just don't get enough exercise, sir.
You say something, Aika?!
Nothing, sir.
Are you guys all right? We were getting tired of waiting!
Oh, my sweet honey!
Gusto! You're alive?
We're outta here!
Huh?
In the middle of the shining city
The sounds were erased by the sounds of the bells and honks
Do you remember that day's heartbeat
And the fingertips that I felt were very sad
If I count the stars and sigh, you overflow
Since more strong feelings are forming little by little
Starting tomorrow it's going to be a new me
I might take a detour by getting lost and by dreaming
But I want to meet your smile at my destination
Since more strong feelings are forming little by little
Starting tomorrow it's going to be a new me
I might take a detour by getting lost and by dreaming
But I want to meet your smile at my destination