Today's chef's special entrée is...
Is something wrong, President?
Well, I was thinking that we haven't done this for a long time.
What?
I mean, eating dinner together like this.
Yeah, that's very true, President.
It's okay to call me Papa now.
Oh, that's right.
I don't come to this kind of place so often, so I'm nervous.
You're a funny girl.
That's everything. Please take extra care during this operation.
I'll be awaiting good news.
Yes, I will certainly bring good news.
Aika and Michikusa are late.
Hey, Rion,
what are your plans for the future?
What?
Are you going to continue working as a Salvager?
What are you talking about? Of course I will.
I don't think that's a good idea.
What?
Why not, Papa?
The world has become a better place in recent days.
It's time for you to plan your future more seriously.
A Salvager is one who searches for an inheritance from the past.
People shouldn't do that kind of work forever, Rion.
You should find something better...
No way! That's not true!
I don't have any intention of quitting this job!
I like being a Salvager!
I'll continue doing this job with you and Aika!
I'll never quit!
Rion...
President...
Oh, Michikusa, you're here.
Where is Aika?
She said she couldn't make it.
I see.
No way! You're kidding, right?
Now I'm annoyed!
I worked for four hours on this and was just about to finish.
Oh, I hate this!
The constellations that decorate the summer night
The diamonds start to twinkle
Letting go into the time
I want to warm the body, tired from swimming
I pretended not to notice the smile that hides the loneliness
If it's an endless dream (keep on going)
Fight and shine
Believe in your true self (it's up to you)
Over and over
Look only at the irreplaceable future
Decisive Break-in! Delmo Base!
Damn it!
Thank you for the dinner.
Sure, see you later. Be careful going home!
Good night.
Night.
That was delicious!
Aika should have skipped work and joined us.
I guess so.
That's...
Wait!
Rion!
Papa! Papa!
President!
Three, two, one!
What?
Our office is gone.
Ah, Rion, here you are.
Um, what happened to the office?
Hey, what happened?
Can't you see? It collapsed.
The Delmos blew it up.
Oh, is that so?
I was just surprised, because I came here,
and I saw the office, and it's gone.
By the way, where's the boss?
In the hospital.
What?
The Delmos hit him with a car,
and it'll take him four months to heal.
Oh, no. Then, what about Aika?
Don't be so sad! You shouldn't be like this, Rion.
She's dead now. We can't do anything about it.
She's not coming back even if you cry for her.
Who said she's dead?! You bastard!
But...
She's not dead! Aika wouldn't die this way!
I'm sure she's still alive!
Ouch.
Where are you going, Rion?
I'm going to the Delmo's hideout!
I'll find where it is, and break into it.
I must have revenge for Aika and Papa.
I'll see you later!
Uh? Did you forget something, Rion?
You're coming with me!
Ouch! That hurts, Rion!
Aika! Oh, Aika!
Tell me this is a lie, Aika!
Ah, how long are you going to do this?
You're really annoying me.
But...
I know, I know. I understand you were serious about her.
But crying doesn't change anything.
Act like a man!
Shut up!
You'll never understand that my sadness is deeper than the ocean.
Aika! My honey!
Oh, I see. So sorry.
Even if your body is grown up, your mind is still like a baby.
Why didn't this happen to the old man instead of her?
Aika!
I should have asked her out to dinner at least once.
Hey, walk by yourself.
Can I politely refuse to take revenge?
Hey, Rion! Rion!
What did you say?!
Are you really going to get revenge?
You idiot! What are you thinking?
I'm not an idiot!
How can I just take this shit and do nothing?
Hey, can you give me some help? Please!
I refuse!
Why should I poke my nose into another company's problems?
I feel sorry about Aika, and your office.
You have my sympathies, but this and that are different.
What if something bad were to happen to you too?
Don't make your father worried or even more sad!
That's right.
No! I said I'll do it, so I will!
You can't stop me!
There's no way I can forgive the Delmos!
Fine! You don't have to help me! I'll get revenge for Aika myself!
I'm sure Papa will understand my feelings too!
Hey! Why don't you say something to her, Gusto?
All right! I understand. I'll help you, Rion!
Bandra got angry and left. Is it okay?
That won't matter at all!
I'm the one who decided to help her.
Now you guys can completely rely on me.
Then, let's find out the Delmo's hideout!
We're counting on you, Gusto!
What's wrong, Gusto?
Well, managing intelligence data was all handled by Bandra.
I have no idea how to do such things, I'm sorry.
What's with that? How can I rely on your empty brain?!
It's not like that, Rion!
By the way, I know somebody
who's very familiar with that kind of information.
She may be able to find the Delmo's hideout.
She might even be able to give us help.
She told me that she was a former A-class special secret agent.
Former A-class special secret agent?
Her name is Meipia.
Yo, long time no see, both of you.
What? Oh, you guys knew each other?
Yeah, a little bit.
What can I get for you?
That's it.
Inuboe Island. People call it Lighthouse Island.
I can finally get revenge for Aika.
By the way, couldn't you find a better ship than this?
Don't be silly! This kind of ship is less suspicious than others.
Hey, Michikusa, what are you doing?
A hovercraft is approaching us, so I'm saying hello to them.
Hey!
They're Delmos!
Oh, no! One more from over there.
Hey! What do you mean, this boat is less suspicious? Liar!
Hey, shut up! Shut up!
This is no time to fight! They're surrounding us!
We knew this might happen, so we were watching you guys.
I want all of you to die here.
Prepare to fire!
Target is that pleasure boat about four hundred meters ahead.
Faster! Faster! They're gaining on us!
Of course they are. Their ship is much faster than this.
Ouch!
I'm still alive. Was I saved?
So was everybody else.
But how?
What happened...
to these guys?
I found something useful.
Oh, this is perfect for battle.
How do I look?
Do I look cute this time?
Michikusa, you are...
You are such an idiot!
Damn it! Let's go everybody!
What's the matter?
There's an intruder.
What kind?
We're confirming that now.
All right, this is gonna be our avenging battle for Aika!
Let's destroy everything, Rion!
Oops!
Damn it!
I've got it.
Intruders are now moving from F block to the third floor of E block.
All right. Close gates number 5, 7, 8, and 16!
We'll lure them into one area.
Roger! I'll seal gates number 5, 7, 8, and 16.
Michikusa, what are you doing? Hurry!
Right.
They're trapped.
What's wrong?
What?
What's this?
You don't suppose...
Yes, you guys were tricked by us.
You guys!
My, if it isn't you two, Miss Aika's appendix.
What do you mean by appendix?!
But she's got us pegged.
Don't agree with her!
Were you guys planning to take revenge for Aika Sumeragi?
Are those two your bodyguards?
We're...
So what? Come on and fight me!
Oh, my, but I'm afraid that's impossible.
Your opponents this time are...
We are your opponents!
Golden Delmo Sania!
Likewise, Tonia!
Here we go!
Come on! Here we go!
Come on!
Don't think we're so easy!
You guys aren't even a threat anymore, with Aika Sumeragi gone.
Now I'm pissed!
What is this?
Commander...
Hang in there! I'll call for help right now.
Blue-haired woman...
Blue hair?
Commander!
What should we do about these people?
Considering what they did, they have to pay dearly.
What? Why don't you kill us if you want to?!
Then I will make your wish come true.
I'm okay. I have no intention of dying yet.
Oh, me neither.
Hey!
Don't worry, I'll kill everybody together.
Rion...
Miss Aika must be waiting eagerly for everybody to join her.
Too bad! But I'm not dead yet.
Aika, I knew you were alive!
Huh? Aika?
Sorry to have made you worry, Rion.
Damn you! Aika Sumeragi!
How many times have you disturbed us? But this time it ends!
That's exactly what I intend. Let's end this here.
Let me take care of this, please.
Aika!
Here.
I'm glad. This was my favorite one.
Thank you, Rion.
Tonia!
Tonia...
Rie...
Sania...
Take this!
Aika!
It can't be!
No way!
Aika!
Commander!
We'll abandon this base, and destroy it.
But, commander, if we lose the base, how do we...
We can't hurt our comrades any more!
I'm ordering to end the operation against Aika Sumeragi.
I also prohibit any further contact with Aika Sumeragi from now on.
Commander! Are you sure you want to do this?
We will start over from the beginning.
But when the time comes,
I will settle this myself.
Attention! We're abandoning this base!
All personnel will evacuate this base immediately!
Yes, ma'am!
I'm glad. I'm really glad.
Hey! Who is that?
I've gone back to living in a trailer again.
There is nothing we can do about it. It's just that way.
But our President seems to be recovering faster than expected.
Let's work hard together.
I know that, but...
Oh, Rion. If you're concerned about something, I will be of help.
What are you saying? It's about you! You!
Ah, my kappa doll.
Are you aware of our situation?
Oh, ouch! Please don't do that! It hurts.
Now, now, you two.
Hey! I'll see you later!
So dance with me tonight
I am not above being cool for a while
Baby, tell me what you want, what you want
In the hardest time, you still look so good to me
Maybe I can ease your mind, ease your mind
And you have your fears just like every man
Cannot be sure of yourself all the time
Just close your eyes, I'll turn the music on
Now you're gonna do what you got to do
So dance with me tonight, 'cause I make you feel all right
Who fell in love at sight? I don't want to make a fight
Just dance with me tonight, if you wanna hold me tight
Don't say maybe, come to me
So dance with me tonight, 'cause I make you feel all right
Who fell in love at sight? I don't want to make a fight
Just dance with me tonight, if you wanna hold me tight
Don't say maybe, come to me