During this age where Tokyo was submerged
due to a change in the earth's crust,
there are professionals who specialize in collecting
companies' secrets and national treasures
that disappeared into the ocean.
They are called the Salvagers.
Aika Sumeragi is one of the prettiest amongst the Salvagers.
And I, Rion Aida, am her pretty assistant.
But Neina, who controls the army of pretty girls called the Delmogeny,
stands against our K2 corporation.
Behind her was the conspiracy planned by her brother,
Rudolph Hargen.
He had a crazy plan of trying to wipe out humankind
with the power of the mysterious Raggu.
Due to that plan, we faced a series of difficulties.
We were in a mad deficit!
Gosh, what are we going to do?
But that was finally settled.
From now on, I am going to pull together our K2 Corporation,
and make it really big!
I don't want to become a lost sheep with frightened eyes
Even though my heart has no room to trust something or save someone
There are times when things change when I go against my destiny
I can't give up
Even if tomorrow carries the cross of yesterday and continues to grieve
Even if I try to find the meaning of life
And just capriciously recite justice
I need to blindfold the depression and start walking
Until the time I take back the glory
The distress of the blue world
The skyscraper in the dark
I sleep by holding the sin and punishment
After my dream and freedom
In order to not repeat the broken tenderness
Listen to the words the wind whispers
And begin tomorrow once again
Aika, you're so cool!
Moving
There we go...
What are you doing, looking at an old promotional video?
Our company used to profit a lot during these days, didn't it?
You were able to make cool videos like this one.
Yeah, I guess.
There were those times too.
Putting that aside, stop fooling around and help.
You should let the newcomer help.
See, he's Michitaro Michikusa.
Resume
It's Shuntaro.
He's so cute.
Yeah.
He looks like a model.
I feel like I saw him on a magazine that my brother used to buy.
Really?
Let's have him take a picture with us.
Yeah.
Um, can you take a picture with us?
Okay, sure.
Let's go.
Yeah.
If you're that slow, the sun's going to set!
Gosh, youngsters these days won't do anything unless they're told!
Although it is a lease, we were finally able
to get an office building for our K2 Corporation.
Textless opening theme
Textless ending theme
(Imaginary Version)
Now you're completely part of me, I don't want to hold back anymore
I remember, we got GD
If curiosity moves in the point of the compass
Then most likely the special power will arise
Silent city, we're salvager
I will one day find the skyscraper of the submerged city
Don't be afraid, come together
By passing through time, let's revive
All the things that the sun shines upon
I miss you
I want to convey it to you, I don't want you to forget
I take you
Since there is a world awaiting that no one has ever seen
Let it go
Always
Let's leave the noisy city
I want to get rid of the boots and walk with the wind
By taking a deep breath in and out
The innocent feeling that I forgot awakened
If I rest my chin on my hand near the moon window, I think of you
Until yesterday, I was pretending not to notice
The thing that I was hiding deep down in my heart
Since I am more pure than I appear to be
I was always caught in between toughness and shyness
In the middle of the shining city
The sounds were erased by the sounds of the bells and honks
Do you remember that day's heartbeat
And the fingertips that I felt were very sad
If I count the stars and sigh, you overflow
Since more strong feelings are forming little by little
Starting tomorrow it's going to be a new me
I might take a detour by getting lost and by dreaming
But I want to meet your smile at my destination
Since more strong feelings are forming little by little
Starting tomorrow it's going to be a new me
I might take a detour by getting lost and by dreaming
But I want to meet your smile at my destination
Until yesterday, I was pretending not to notice
The thing that I was hiding deep down in my heart
I will start running by holding on to the blue hunch of being
Smoothly able to convey my present feelings
So please wait
News Special
The producer was called a pervert.
After a hot argument
The person in charge is teased as being too curious.
No restriction even for those under age 18
The Aika which shocked various areas finally became a movie.
That
AIKa
Finally became a movie!!
I, Aika Sumeragi, am a skilled Salvager.
With my partner Rion, we will take any dangerous job.
Production: Studio Fantasia
Bandai Visual
The stupid and perverted Gusto and his partner, Bandra.
But when it comes to mechanics, they are experts.
Director: Katsuhiko Nishijima
He gets in the way a lot and we have an unfortunate relationship.
Today's another tug of war with Hargen and his army.
Character design: Noriyasu Yamauchi
How should I handle these annoying guys?
White Leader
But wait, that's out of character.
Master Hargen
Plus, aren't I the main character?
What waits for us
on the path to love...
What gets in the way of love? What do you mean, love?
Well, anyways, coming soon to theaters in the summer!
Coming soon to theaters in the summer!
Of course it's a lie.
Of course it's a lie
Moving
There.
A promotional video?
Yes! A promotional video!
A Salvager's top notch skill and achievement.
The gorgeous Aika and the pretty me.
We have all the qualifications in order to get back our past glory.
All we have to do now is create an awesome promotional video
and do massive advertisement.
If we do all that, then we'll get a lot of business,
and we'll make a lot of money!
Even if we got that much business,
we don't have the capacity to handle it all.
Shut up!
You're still a newcomer! You don't understand anything!
You're so cocky!
Okay!
It has to be a promotional video!
For example...
We got involved in an international terrorist group's
plan to explode the city,
and we battled face to face against the terrorists.
Thanks to Aika's and my achievements,
the terrorists were defeated and the incident was solved.
But we're Salvagers, aren't we?
Why do we have to do something so 007-ish?
You're still a newcomer!
You don't understand anything!
You're so cocky!
Wow, how nostalgic.
How young!
Dr. Hargen's ambition is finally revealed
We have to do something! Something, Aika!
With the power of Raggu
Got it! Let's stop Dr. Hargen.
Creation of Heaven and Earth!!
I'm gonna fight too, in the name of a Salvager.
Stop it!
Salvagers AIKa and Rion
Finally, the climax!
For the Earth
Original Video Animation
A Flower Blooming in Space
Aika Trial 4.
Wow! The series is going to continue.
Responding to your demand, the extension of the series has been decided.
Touchy adventure!!
Dr. Hargen's ambition is finally revealed
We have to do something! Something, Aika!
With the power of Raggu
Got it! Let's stop Dr. Hargen.
Creation of Heaven and Earth!!
I'm gonna fight too, in the name of a Salvager.
Stop it!
Salvagers AIKa and Rion
For the Earth
Oh no! Oh no! Oh no!
Everyone is getting caught, the ship is about to explode,
and Aika, who is fighting against the altered human, is...
Aika! You look...
Rion, I didn't want to show it to you.
So cool!
Original Video Animation
A Flower Blooming in Space
It's finally the climax.
Aika Trial 4.
Responding to your demand, the extension of the series has been decided.
Touchy adventure!!
The series is going to continue.
Now you're completely part of me, I don't want to hold back anymore
I remember, we got GD
If curiosity moves in the point of the compass
Then most likely the special power will arise
Silent city, we're salvager
I will one day find the skyscraper of the submerged city
Don't be afraid, come together
By passing through time, let's revive
All the things that the sun shines upon
I miss you
I want to convey it to you, I don't want you to forget
I take you
Since there is a world awaiting that no one has ever seen
Let it go
Always
I'm looking for the Silent City
I want to stare at each other by passing time
I don't have regrets over the things I lost
I remember, we got GD
If I could be innocent as nakedness
I can live with a special power
Silent city, we're salvager
Someday your voice will be heard in the submerged city
Don't be afraid, come together
The power of the rainbow that lights
The secret darkness where the golden wind blows
I miss you
My hands are full with dreams about you
Stay for me
The unexplored silent diamond that no one knows
You can get
Certainly
I miss you
I want to convey it to you, I don't want you to forget
I take you
Since there is a world awaiting that no one has ever seen
Let it go
Always
Moving
If we were going to make a promotional video,
I would want to film Aika after she transformed.
That's right!
Our selling point that no other company will have.
Aika...
No way.
Don't say that.
Please, please.
If I say no, it means no.
We can't use it for that.
That's what I thought.
By the way, be sure you help after lunch.
Oh yeah!
In place of Aika, I will...
Rion has been cornered and caught in a desperate situation.
Right then...
That might be a little embarrassing.
You get used to it.
If you get used to it, it's not a big deal.
Oh, is that how it is?
That's how it is.
Oh, you're eating lunch.
Hey, boss, where were you?
Well, y'know.
Boss!
There is lunch for you.
Hey, Daddy.
Let's make a promotional video.
Promotional video?
A promotional video?
That sounds good!
Really?
Aika, he said it's okay!
A promotional video needs a song!
Huh? A song?
It's my fault that you have bad luck
From now on, I'll risk my life to support you
Your teary eyes are pretty
Your kindness blends in
I worry you
You are my desire
Only you are my treasure
Bear the storm and the dream will blossom
Time will help the dream blossom
Softly, softly enjoy the happiness tonight
Even if it is dark
Even if everything is second-hand
Someday please build your own office building
Bear life and dream will blossom
It's small, but the dream will blossom
We have high hopes for tomorrow
Studio Fantasia / Bandai Visual
Aika's second season starts with a new plot!!
The Hargen incident was solved and six months have passed.
I am a prince.
Yay, if I walk, the girls turn around.
The K2 Corporation returned to its regular Salvager job
The
Plot
Action!
and was leading an ordinary day.
Then one day...
I am so popular. It's a huge problem...
Pretty girls
Since we finally got to this point, let's take a break.
Cute boys
And then...
To tell the truth, I have reserved a room at a resort hotel.
Aika and the others get attacked by the evil hands of the newly-revived Delmo organization!!
Hey, Michikusa, the next one is going to take place on an island.
Hurray! Daddy, you're awesome!
We decided to take a vacation on an island.
Is that true, Rion?
A southern island
sounds good.
The mysterious Golden Delmo
A heroic battle
takes place on
the southern island!!
But what awaited us was a trap.
But it becomes
a big deal.
led by the newly-revived Delmo organization
A heroic battle
takes place on
the southern island!!
Huh? What's
going to happen?
Aika becomes
this and that...
A heroic battle
takes place on
the southern island!!
We got caught in their trap and faced a crisis
Ahhh! I can't say it.
Aika's greatest danger!!
You want to hear it, don't you?
Huh?
Then that's fine.
Aika, next trial.
Yes, I do.
The Golden Delmo Operation
If you can't say it, then that's fine.
Oh, time's up!
Romance and the trap get heated under the strong southern sunlight.
If you want to know the rest, then watch the next episode.
Please watch it.
Can't miss it!!