As discussed, we've decided to perform operation "Golden Apple".
Miss Bianca...
I want you to be in charge of this operation.
Thank you very much.
As you know, the goal of this mission is to capture the target alive,
so we can use it for our research material.
Yes.
Did you get information as to her whereabouts?
Yes, of course.
I'll be waiting for the good news.
Yes, ma'am!
The constellations that decorate the summer night
The diamonds start to twinkle
Letting go into the time
I want to warm the body, tired from swimming
I pretended not to notice the smile that hides the loneliness
If it's an endless dream (Keep on going)
Fight and shine
Believe in your true self (It's up to you)
Over and over
Look only at the irreplaceable future
The Golden Delmo Operation
Lately, work's been getting done quite satisfactorily. Hasn't it?
Yes, it has.
Well, thank you for all your hard work.
You worked hard too.
Actually, I have something to tell everyone.
Since we came a long way to the south...
To show my appreciation for all of you,
I made plans to stay one night at a resort hotel on Peroronka Island.
Papa, really?!
Don't call me Papa. Call me President!
Can we afford it, President?
Sure, our company has been doing better recently.
I thought I should return something to my employees.
You're the best!
Are you sure?
Here they come.
Gorgeous!
Well, it's all right.
I made a reservation under the name of the K2 Corporation.
Yes, sir.
We reserved the rooms for you.
This is super cool.
It's very nice!
I could sure live here.
Yahoo!
Wow!
Aika, let's go to the pool! The pool!
All right. Can you wait a minute?
If I don't use a lot of this, I'll be very sorry later.
Where's Papa?
He told me he had to go somewhere.
I see. He is probably doing that.
"That?"
I win!
That's mean, Rion!
Oh, excuse me.
I'm very sorry.
Oh, no. Don't worry about it.
Can you bring the same drink for this lady?
Thank you very much.
No, I'm the one who caused you trouble.
You must have just arrived at this hotel today.
How can you tell?
Because there's no way I could've overlooked such a beautiful woman.
My, you're quite the charmer.
May I have your name? If you don't mind...
My name is Pierre Valimore.
I'm Aika. Aika Sumeragi.
What an exotic name!
You must be related to some noble family.
Well, I'm not sure.
Have you been staying here long, Mr. Valimore?
Please call me Pierre.
Been here long, Pierre?
Yes, I'm here for vacation, but I was getting bored recently.
Then a beautiful woman like you showed up.
This certainly is good fortune.
You really are a charmer.
I can only tell the truth.
Rion, there...
Aika...
They're going to do it, aren't they?
Why are we going through so much trouble to capture one woman?
I wouldn't be satisfied by just physically capturing her.
I need to completely humiliate her.
What's wrong with you? You're in a bad mood.
It seems Aika is a rather imprudent person.
Perhaps she's feeling a bit liberated, here on the southern island.
I mean running off with such a cheap, flashy guy.
Maybe you should find a nice guy too, Rion.
Excuse me.
I'm a little lost. Which way is the elevator?
Go over there, and make a left...
Really? We're also from Tokyo!
Well, we're going to the beach now. Do you want to come with us?
Okay.
Let's go and let's do!
All right! One more round. Give me the chips.
We captured two of the targets.
We are also holding the last target.
All right. We're about to head back there.
Did they go somewhere?
Is anything wrong?
Well, my companions aren't there.
They might be in the restaurant.
I guess so.
No, I'm not.
I'm not usually such an impulsive woman.
Something is wrong with me today.
Yes, yes, I understand.
I guess the southern ocean has a strange effect on people.
It does, doesn't it? It must.
Excuse me for a moment.
I feel really strange today.
It can happen to anyone.
Pierre, you are really a gentleman.
You don't know about my true nature.
Oh, here, it's here.
This is not good, Pierre... Having your way with a drunk woman.
It's not like a gentleman.
Who are you people?
What's going on?
This is the answer.
That uniform...
Aika Sumeragi, I've been waiting for this moment.
Pierre, get out of here!
I will share a secret with you first.
A woman!
Everything has worked out as we planned.
Why did you do this?
For revenge!
Look down there.
Rion!
First, you'll watch your friends struggle in pain.
They'll die! They'll die!
Well, if you want to save them...
What are you doing?!
I'm awake now!
The drug isn't working on her?!
Miss Bianca, the purpose of this mission is...
I know!
She was a woman...
I've already kissed her!
Aika!
They're all Hargen's people!
I know.
They're trying to get revenge for him.
What?! Revenge?!
What is Hargen?
Well...
It would take a long time to explain,
but let's just say, they're the villains!
Over there!
Thank you.
You're welcome.
It seems like Hargen's people are all over this hotel.
What should we do, Aika?
We have to find the president first, and then get out of here.
Was that guy also working for them, Aika?
Oh, please don't bring that up.
I knew it!
That guy wasn't a guy, he's a girl.
What?!
Go on ahead!
But...
Get going!
I was really fooled by you.
You've never seen such a gorgeous guy as me, have you?
Quite true!
Miss Valerie!
Do it!
I wouldn't be satisfied, just shooting you dead.
Is that so?
Damn it!
This is Bianca. Request a mobile unit air strike!
Roger! We will rush to get over there.
What's that?
Then what's Aika doing?
Well...
What the hell is that?!
It appears to be an armored car.
I can tell that by looking!
I mean, why did it suddenly appear out of nowhere?!
Aren't I your target?
Aika!
Good! Move out!
Yes, Miss Bianca.
Why did she have to take my job?
What is this water?
We're drowning!
President!
Aika!
You guys stay here.
Papa!
What's your plan?
There's another one. Get in quickly!
We won't beat them this way!
I've got an idea.
Aika!
Stupid!
We did it!
That was an easy ending.
Miss Bianca!
No!
Aika!
Well, this turned out to be a terrible vacation.
Indeed.
I guess Hargen's people could attack us at any time.
There's trouble ahead.
What is this Hargen?
Well...
A guy named Hargen planned to rule the earth using the power of Raggu.
What is Raggu?
Eh? Raggu?... Well, that is...
The operation failed.
I assume Aika and her companions already escaped from the island.
I see.
As I thought, she wasn't so easy to handle.
Let's take the next action immediately.
Yes, ma'am!
Operation "Silver Wild Grapevine" is already prepared.
Excellent!
So dance with me tonight
I am not above being cool for a while
Baby, tell me what you want, what you want
In the hardest time, you still look so good to me
Maybe I can ease your mind, ease your mind
And you have your fears just like every man
Cannot be sure of yourself all the time
Just close your eyes, I'll turn the music on
Now you're gonna do what you got to do
So dance with me tonight, 'cause I make you feel all right
Who fell in love at sight? I don't want to make a fight
Just dance with me tonight, if you wanna hold me tight
Don't say maybe, come to me
So dance with me tonight, 'cause I make you feel all right
Who fell in love at sight? I don't want to make a fight
Just dance with me tonight, if you wanna hold me tight
Don't say maybe, come to me
A big company hires the K2 Corporation for an investigation,
so we head north.
Arriving at their installation,
we meet a beautiful young girl, an ace fighter pilot.
To test my compatibility with the Probe-jet,
she requests that I take a pre-flight exam.
What does this girl intend to do to Aika?
Man, this is totally suspicious!
After thoroughly examining me, the Delmos reveal themselves.
While escaping with my data,
the beautiful young Delmo girl launches a cunning attack.
Aika, next trial:
Delmo Operation: "White Silver"
The heat from this fierce battle with the beautiful Delmo
could even melt snow.