Aika!
Hang in there, Aika! Hey!
Hand that woman over to us!
Shit! Reinforcements.
Aika...
Idiot! What do you think you're doing?
If you go out there, you'll just end up getting caught too!
Just wait here and see what happens.
I figured this was going to happen!
Bandra!
Hey! What's the big idea?!
Oh, well, guess they're gone.
Don't just say "they're gone!" What do I do now?!
Good question.
Now you're completely part of me, I don't want to hold back anymore
I remember, we got GD
If curiosity moves in the point of the compass
Then most likely the special power will arise
Silent city, we're salvager
I will one day find the skyscraper of the submerged city
Don't be afraid, come together
By passing through time, let's revive
All the things that the sun shines upon
I miss you
I want to convey it to you, I don't want you to forget
I take you
Since there is a world awaiting that no one has ever seen
Let it go
Always
Well? You coming or not?
Look, just close the duct after me, okay?
I'll go! I'll go! I'll go with you!
Aika, what on Earth are you...
Ultranate metal...
I take it she isn't naked 'cause you two were having fun, right?
Bandra, you know something about this?
Well, a little.
Even with their lame-ass shooting, they managed to hit something!
I'll put us down on some nearby land.
Propulsion system control.
Disengaged.
Separation bolt.
Arming.
Separation!
Separation light, green!
Continue pitch up.
Flight module, confirmed.
Docking procedure, start.
Roll, pitch, yaw, dead on target.
Docking in seven...
Six...
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One...
Capture!
Hull latch, engage.
Raggu engine flight module, docking completed.
Emit Raggu energy now.
Yes, sir.
So, who are you, anyway? Where are we going?
C'mon, tell me! Are you listening to me?
Listen, you...
You're a spy, but you actually carry business cards?!
And what is an "International Crisis Management Treaty
Authority Organization, World Secret Agent League,
Special Expeditionary Foreign Affairs Division" anyway?!
A class A agent, huh?
So, where are we going, Miss Class A Agent Meipia?
To the Regulus' hangar bay.
We may be able to lose the guys after us and escape.
Ooh, no wonder you're a class A agent! You're so cool!
Be quiet and follow me, or I'll leave you behind!
Right, right.
Aika!
So, how did Gozo get hurt then?
There are all sorts of rumors about that guy.
He never talks about what happened back then.
Nobody knows the truth about him.
Aika! Are you okay?
Where's Rion?
Well, about that, Aika...
Where is Rion?
Where's Rion?! What's happened to her?!
There was nothing else I could do. Rescuing you was all I could manage.
You left her!
Aika!
What do you think you're doing, Aika?!
I'm going to save Rion...
Rion... I have to save her!
Aika!
You're still not back to full strength. Don't push yourself.
Rion... I have to save Rion...
Aika...
All right, we'll do it. But first we get you strong again.
Of course! Food! Let's have something to eat!
Cut it out, you old hag! You're scaring the fish away!
Cut the crap, Bandra!
You're set on going back?
In the end, you're just a little kid at heart.
This "I've gotta save her" line. Just 'cause you're sweet for a girl!
You're gonna die! Die! You're just gonna die!
Shut up! I don't care! I don't care! I wanna do this!
Oh, yeah? Oh, yeah? Go on. Go on.
Just one thing, though! I'm not going with you! Do you hear me?!
Fine, don't come! I won't let you come!
Fine! I'm outta here!
I see. I'll head out there myself, then.
And keep Aika from doing anything crazy before I arrive, Bandra.
You heard what your boss said.
Data on the Raggu.
I don't want to have a debt with you.
Hmpf! I hate your type!
Rion...
Big brother...
I didn't want you to see me fail like that.
Enough. Don't worry about it.
I've a favor to ask of you.
I made this based off of the one that woman had.
Your very own, personal Ultranate metal.
Several times more powerful than the original.
You'll wear it, won't you, Neina?
Good girl.
It suits you so well, Neina.
Does it, big brother?
Nice, Neina...
Yes? Roger.
Mr. Hargen, we have a transmission from the Naval Chief.
Couldn't wait any longer, could you?
This is a formal request. Hand over the Raggu, Hargen.
I'm afraid I cannot.
We're prepared to use force, if necessary.
As you wish.
That material is too valuable to give to stupid apes like you.
I will put it to much more effective use, I assure you.
Bastard, you won't get away with...
I've no time to listen to the chattering of apes.
What's the matter?!
After you destroy it, get out on your own. Good luck.
Meipia?
Hey, wait!
C'mon, what's wrong?
Wait! What's the big idea?!
Cabin pressure!
Auto.
Oxygen regulator!
Normal.
Flood lights!
On.
Repressurization switch!
Safe!
Captain, Mr. Hargen's coming in.
Right. Roger.
Onboard speakers, on plus 2.
To all crew and staff members.
This ship is now moving into the operation's final stage.
After we reach the stratosphere,
we'll hit the Earth with the Raggu Beam.
However, this operation will not result in destruction.
Raggu energy rolls back the effects of entropy,
and will result in the purification of the entire Earth.
I repeat, this operation will destroy nothing!
Since the dawn of time, humanity has inflicted
great suffering upon Mother Earth.
We now perform a ceremony for the atonement of all mankind!
Catherine!
C'mon! Shake a leg, will ya?!
Would you get off of me?!
Well, you pulled me down here, didn't you?
Glasses, glasses... Where are my glasses?
This is that room from when we...
This is the Raggu reactor, the ship's main power source.
Eight ships sighted ahead of us!
In formation, with a heavy ship in the center!
They've come.
Sound the alarm for battle stations!
Raggu impingement shield, on!
Ships sighted blocking our course. I think it's the national fleet.
Take us in.
Aye! Raggu engines, ahead full thrust!
Yikes! The output's rising!
What can I do to stop this thing?!
Enemy ships have opened fire!
Take evasive action.
It doesn't matter. I'll teach those apes a lesson they need.
Return fire now.
Ready all guns! Target the central ship of the formation ahead!
Plot firing solution!
Enemy shots, impacting!
No way...
They got us!
Direct hit, forward deck!
No damage.
Enemy vessels, firing second salvo!
Ready the main guns to fire!
Load main guns with Raggu shells!
Firing solution, input!
Fire main guns!
Impact in 24 seconds!
Enemy shots, impacting!
This is Meipia! What's with this bombardment?! I'm still on board!
This was a political decision.
Shit! They're abandoning me!
Direct hit, astern to port! No damage!
Attention! Our shots are impacting!
Main ship, vaporized. #4 light ship, dead in the water.
The remaining vessels are retreating.
It worked!
We did it!
Well, there it is. So, what are we supposed to do now?
Go in close.
Don't blame me if this doesn't work!
All hands to stations! Flight configuration!
Main wing, ready for takeoff position! Gear down!
What's up with that?! It just turned into a rocket!
You mean that thing can fly?!
Leak check. Cockpit pressure?
Auto.
Cabin pressure?
Air data processors?
On.
Anti-ice?
Takeoff checklist, completed.
Until we reach rotation speed, engine failure will cancel takeoff.
If anything happens after takeoff, we'll perform an emergency landing.
Right.
My control.
Your control.
Runway clear!
Clear for takeoff!
Holy Fox, launch!
Power set, takeoff position!
Power, set!
All right, engine temp normal.
They're going to fly?
Hey, what do you mean, "fly"? What's gonna fly?!
Hey, what did you do? Come on!
Just take a look up there.
Engine bay doors, open!
What?
If they stay open during take-off, they'll be destroyed!
Shut them, quickly!
I can't! The emergency system in the engine bay has activated!
We can't override it from here!
I'll go.
One aircraft, approaching from astern!
Forget it! Let it go!
See you!
What do you mean, "see you"?! What about me?!
I'm afraid this is only built for one, sorry.
Too bad.
Why, you! Hey! Lemme go, you idiot!
Like hell I'll let go!
You... You... You!
Meipia!
She's dead.
Well, serves her right, trying to escape by herself.
Okay, just let us down like this.
Hurry up!
Aika...
Aika!
Gusto!
What are you doing?! Get going! It's closing!
We'll stay here!
VR!
Rotation set!
No! Stop it! You pervert!
Hey!
What, you still alive, Gusto?
This is...
We meet again.
Welcome back.
In the middle of the shining city
The sounds were erased by the sounds of the bells and honks
Do you remember that day's heartbeat
And the fingertips that I felt were very sad
If I count the stars and sigh, you overflow
Since more strong feelings are forming little by little
Starting tomorrow it's going to be a new me
I might take a detour by getting lost and by dreaming
But I want to meet your smile at my destination
Since more strong feelings are forming little by little
Starting tomorrow it's going to be a new me
I might take a detour by getting lost and by dreaming
But I want to meet your smile at my destination
Now that I've gotten back on board Hargen's ship,
I see that Neina has been changed by the power of Ultranate metal.
In the face of its unstoppable attack,
my body can only cry out in pain.
What's wrong? You want to beg me for your life?
Meanwhile, Hargen's terrifying project begins to move,
with the aim of recreating the greatest earthquake in history.
We are the ideal of mankind.
We'll create a utopia!
Forget it! You can't tell me what to do!
Aika, next trial:
A Flower Blooming in Space
"A Flower Blooming in Space"
A shining aurora leads the way to destruction.