As I just explained, the purpose of this operation
is to collect all physical data, including her ability to transform.
Merely collecting more data on her seems like a halfway measure.
Is that so?
You can't fight without knowing your enemy.
Our past failures are a case in point.
Precisely.
Furthermore, I will join this operation, to observe first-hand.
Commander, that's too risky!
You might come into contact with the target.
I want to observe her myself.
Besides, executive commanders who always remain in safe places
garner no respect.
Understood.
Then you intend to collect the data yourself?
I'll be accompanied by someone who has already been studying the target.
Yes.
Yes, the target's research is proceeding.
I think I can give you a report very soon.
Oh, really?!
Yes, I'll be right there.
I can collect data first-hand.
The constellations that decorate the summer night
The diamonds start to twinkle
Letting go into the time
I want to warm the body, tired from swimming
I pretended not to notice the smile that hides the loneliness
If it's an endless dream (Keep on going)
Fight and shine
Believe in your true self (It's up to you)
Over and over
Look only at the irreplaceable future
Delmo Operation: White Silver
We are a private enterprise,
currently working for another government as a contractor.
We are here because we've encountered a situation
that we can't handle by ourselves.
Oh, I see.
Super activation materials,
encased in variably structured ceramics and magnetically sealed.
We call it Matoryoshika.
I see.
During the great land submergence, our institution sank.
Since that time, the Matoryoshika has been lost.
The map we had before was completely useless.
We've investigated several times, but our operators couldn't find it.
So we would like to get the famous special A-rank salvager,
Ms. Aika Sumeragi's help.
We'll soon arrive at the remains of our Air Force base.
Wow!
It's all white.
Base preparations?
Completed.
Okay.
Landing altitude determined.
Landing.
Welcome to our base.
I'm Etsuko Mina, I'm the head of this base.
I'm Aika Sumeragi. Pleased to meet you.
We were awaiting your arrival.
Mr. President and Ms. Vice President, thank you for bringing her.
Did anything happen while I was gone?
No, everything is proceeding smoothly.
Good.
This is a very extensive base.
I understand why you wanted an aerial investigation.
That's the probe plane I want you to use.
We remodeled a military spy plane
and built in some high performance probe equipment.
Wow, that's big.
She's just a kid, Aika.
Yes, she is very young.
I'm Rie Petriakov.
I'm Aika Sumeragi, nice to meet you.
I've heard a lot about you.
You must've heard bad things.
You're operating a very powerful plane.
Its maximum speed is Mach 3.2.
There's built-in high performance probe equipment.
You can probe a wide range of areas in a short amount of time.
One more thing, Miss. Aika,
before you operate this plane,
we want you to take a physical and functional examination.
You need adaptability to operate this plane.
It's very simple exam. It won't take long.
Examination? All right.
Rie, I'll let you take care of this.
Yes, ma'am.
Everybody else, please come with me.
Five cm.
Your body is not very flexible, Miss. Aika.
Is it?
Look at me!
Here we go. See, 14 cm.
Right, right. Can we move on to the next test?
Left hand on number 35.
Okay.
Right foot on number 2.
Here we go...
Hey! Do these poses have something to do with flying a plane?
They do.
Next!
I'm sure that girl is doing weird things to Aika.
I'm going to peep inside.
Quietly, quietly.
Don't peep.
All right. Good work.
I'm so tired.
Well, let's move on!
What? Do I have to do more?
Hey, Papa!
That girl Rie must be doing weird things to Aika.
What?
That's why she won't let me in. Something's weird!
I don't think so.
Hey! Why don't you work?
Can't you slow it down a little?
Next! 9 Gs!
Oh, no!
Next! 11 Gs!
Wait a minute!
Take off her clothes and place her on the operating table.
Yes, ma'am.
Now we will start the real examination, Miss Aika.
I will explore your secrets.
Let me show you your accommodations.
All right.
Excuse me, is Miss Sumeragi's examination done yet?
I think it will take a little more time.
Hey!
What's this? What is this thing?
Hey, hey, hey! What is this?
Please stop it. What are you doing?
Please stop!
What's this, eh?
Tell me! What's this?
Please don't do that!
Well? Well? Answer me! Why don't you?
No! No!
Take that!
Ouch!
I thought something was wrong.
This was all a Delmo trick.
I have to tell Aika!
Hey, Michikusa!
Do I look good?
Commander! We're collecting satisfactory data from the target.
Good.
Therefore, you can leave all the remaining work to us.
Are you telling me to go back to headquarters?
How can an Executive Commander leave in the middle of the operation?
But...
Why don't you sit down?
Would you like some tea?
Oh, did you wake up?
I'm sorry. I went a little too far.
Well, are you trying to kill me?
So, can you tell us more about yourself?
I want to hear more too!
Please tell us!
Well, I can't tell you any interesting stories.
Here, drink more.
Oh, I've already had enough.
Don't say that. Please have some.
Are you?
What's wrong, Mr. Aida?
Is anything wrong?
I don't want to seem rude,
but it seems like I've met all of you once before.
Oh, no!
Why don't you sing a song?
We have karaoke in this room.
What?! Oh, really?
Well, why not? Just one song.
You can sing as many songs as you want.
Then, why don't you join me?
Is this switch on?
How's that?
That multi-axis trainer wore me out.
I'm still feeling chest pains.
You were very sexy when you were unconscious.
Don't laugh!
Well then...
She is really a weird girl.
Miss Aika, what do you want to drink?
Do you have beer?
Oh, sorry, I don't have any alcohol.
Then I'll take coffee.
All right!
Aika!
Rion! What's Michikusa doing here too?!
Thank goodness! You're all right!
What do you mean, I'm all right?
Aika! This place isn't a private corporate facility.
This is a Delmo base!
You know, these Delmos?
This girl, Rie, must be a Delmo too! I'm sure of it!
We have to leave here right now, Aika!
Yes, I think we have to leave.
That's right.
You finally found out the truth.
I knew it.
That costume! Rie, you're a...
That's right, Miss Aika!
Golden Delmo, Rie! That's my real name.
You found out the truth very quickly.
But it's all right.
Therefore our story,
about asking your help to investigate the Matoryoshika,
and other things, including this examination to operate the plane,
and of course, everything else was all...
...a lie!
You were so easily fooled.
You look so innocent and cute for an older woman.
If it's a lie, then there must be a real purpose behind this.
Bingo! That's right.
The thing we really wanted to get was...
Ta-daaa! The data on Miss Aika!
Fortunately, I got a full load of your data.
Everything from head to toe.
Now, the last thing I have to take is your fighting data.
Here we go!
Ready?
Action!
This is great! Watching this live is much better.
Aika, you were great!
Oh, she's escaped.
Bye bye!
Hey!
Wait up!
Aika! Your clothes!
Well, well, what's next?
Why are you disturbing me when I'm having fun?
Do it!
Here they come.
Once you decided to do as a man.
Even if people laugh at you.
I'll live my life only one way!
You can't escape anymore.
I wasn't trying to escape.
What did you say?
I've something interesting to show you.
Aika, it's you!
What is this?
I checked every part of your body.
Oh, she's naked.
Michikusa, you don't have to see this!
I'll check inside her body next.
Inside her body?
Anesthesia!
As you see, I've gotten all the data from you.
Why did you do such a thing?
We want to study your strength,
and use it to make our "Delmogeny" even stronger.
I'll never let you do that!
I've already studied the way you fight.
Aika!
Sorry, that's useless.
Now, I have to find my data.
Aika! There's a sign saying "Data Room"!
I guess this is it.
Bingo!
She does make a fast getaway.
Now, I'm really mad!
Rion! Go find the President and prepare to escape!
About forty steps...
Considering Rie's physique, she's about forty meters ahead.
We have to call them when we find the target.
I hope she doesn't come this way.
Hey!
What is it?
The target is approaching. We will hold her off here.
That's not fair!
Uhh! I've got a headache.
Papa!
Oh, Rion!
Michikusa, what the hell are you wearing?!
Terrible danger! Terrible!
You reek of liquor!
How could you drink at a time like this?!
I don't believe you!
Well, it's not so simple to explain.
There's no time to talk about it.
This is an emergency! The base is...
I know. The Delmos tricked us.
They just attacked me.
What happened to Aika?
She told me to prepare to escape and wait for her.
All right. Let's go!
Blue Streak! Come in! Blue Streak! Come in!
Blue Streak! Come in!
This is Red Top! Blue Streak! Come in!
Nobody is responding.
I see.
Rie, what's wrong?
I've got the data. However...
Excellent work, Rie.
We will take care of it from here.
Uh, yes, ma'am.
Are you planning to fight?
I'll go along with you.
She's coming.
Ready?
Yes.
You were all Delmos after all!
Couldn't you tell?
I won't give the data back.
Hargen is gone now. Why must you continue this?!
Yes, Mr. Hargen is gone.
And perhaps we don't need to exist anymore,
since the Delmos were created to serve Mr. Hargen.
But we still have pride.
Aika Sumeragi!
We will defeat you and show our loyalty to Mr. Hargen!
That is our will!
Stop...
No!
Commander!
Idiot!
Cramped...
Rion, it's a little tight, but be patient.
Okay.
I will not let you escape.
Max power!
Rie!
Stop it, Rie!
So dance with me tonight
I am not above being cool for a while
Baby, tell me what you want, what you want
In the hardest time, you still look so good to me
Maybe I can ease your mind, ease your mind
And you have your fears just like every man
Cannot be sure of yourself all the time
Just close your eyes, I'll turn the music on
Now you're gonna do what you got to do
So dance with me tonight, 'cause I make you feel all right
Who fell in love at sight? I don't want to make a fight
Just dance with me tonight, if you wanna hold me tight
Don't say maybe, come to me
So dance with me tonight, 'cause I make you feel all right
Who fell in love at sight? I don't want to make a fight
Just dance with me tonight, if you wanna hold me tight
Don't say maybe, come to me
The Golden Delmo's fierce attack
mercilessly destroys the K2 Corporation and Aika.
Aika! Aika! Aika!
Calm down, Rion!
Papa, Papa, don't you feel anything?
We've lost Aika, and our company.
Don't do anything stupid!
I won't forgive them! I'll never forgive them!
I'll get revenge for Aika! Let's go, Michikusa!
We'll have a battle to avenge Aika!
Rion, wait! Don't be a fool! Don't be so hasty!
Rion breaks into the Delmo base with Gusto and Meipia.
Aika, next trial!
Decisive Break-in! Delmo Base!
A blue flower whirls in jet-black darkness.