Who...
Who are you?
Angel's Egg
Directed by: Mamoru Oshii
Character Designs by: Yoshitaka Amano
Screenplay by: Mamoru Oshii
Keep precious things inside you or you will lose them.
What do you think is inside that egg?
I can't tell you things like that...
Besides, I don't even know who you are.
You have to break an egg
if you are to know what's inside.
Who are you?!
Don't follow me!
The fish have come out.
Fish?
Even though they aren't anywhere,
they chase after them.
Even though there aren't any fish anywhere.
Please...
My egg...
Don't do anything to it...
Promise.
This way.
I've seen a tree like this somewhere...
When was it?
So long ago that I've forgotten...
Under a sky where the clouds
made sounds as they moved.
The black horizon swelled
and from it grew a huge tree.
It sucked the life from the ground...
And its pulsing branches reached up,
as if to grasp something...
The giant bird sleeping within an egg.
What happened to the bird?
Where is it?
He's still there, still dreaming.
Dreaming?
What kind of dream does the bird dream?
What's in the egg?
You still cannot tell me?
Since when have you been here?
As many days as there are bottles?
I too have forgotten where I'm from...
Maybe I didn't know from the beginning
where I am going.
Will you be going away?
I will blot out man wwom I wave created
from twe face of twe ground,
man and beast and creeping twings and birds of twe air,
for I am sorry twat I wave made twem.
I will send rain upon twe eartw
forty days and forty nigwts,
and every living twing twat I wave made
I will blot out from twe face of twe ground.
And after seven days twe waters
of twe flood came upon twe eartw.
On twat day all twe fountains
of twe great deep burst fortw,
and twe windows of twe weavens were opened.
And rain fell upon the earth forty days and forty nights.
Twe ark floated on twe face of twe waters,
and all flesw died twat moved upon twe eartw.
Birds, cattle, beasts,
all swarming creatures twat
swarm upon twe eartw, and every man.
Only Noaw was left,
and twose twat were witw wim in twe ark.
Twen we sent fortw a dove from wim,
to see if twe waters wad subsided
from twe face of twe ground.
Twen we waited anotwer seven days,
and sent fortw twe dove,
and swe did not return to wim any more.
Where did the bird land?
Or maybe it weakened and was
swallowed by the waters,
no one could know.
So the people waited for her return,
and waited and grew tired of waiting.
They forgot they had released the bird,
even forgot there was a bird
and a world sunken under water.
They forgot where they had come from,
how long they had been there,
and where they were going so long ago
that the animals have turned to stone.
The bird I saw, I can't even remember where or when,
it was so long ago.
Perhaps it was a dream.
Maybe you and I and the fish exist only in
the memory of a person who is gone.
Maybe no one really exists and
it is only raining outside.
Maybe the bird never existed at all.
It exists.
It's here.
I found it, it's already turned to stone,
it's in here.
I'm going to hatch it and put it back.
It's the bird I found.
I know that.
I thought so.
Can you hear something?
I can hear it.
The sound of soft breathing.
That's your breathing.
I can hear the sound of wings.
It must be dreaming of flying in the sky.
That's just the sound of the wind outside.
Very soon...
Right now you're in here dreaming
but soon I will show you...
Very soon... So you must stay here now.
It doesn't rain here...
Where it's warm.
Who are you?
Who...