This is Signal, the
greatest robot I've ever created!
Cool! It's a robot in
the form of a human!
It's built with state
of the art technology...
...and also has a fighting
program for combat tactics.
Also, his Mira technology body is
covered with a flexible metal I invented.
So, it's possible to make
more natural, human movement.
Hey, can it move?
Yes.
Do it, do it!
Well, then.
I will program the
personality to your liking.
Let's see...
I want someone
reliable, like a big brother.
I wonder if that will make
him somewhat like a bully.
Well, let's go!
It's perfect.
Here it comes, it's Mira!
That's my big bro.
Yay... yay...
Stop it, I'm tired of the usual praise.
What are you angry about?
Cause I can't catch fish.
Huh, that's boring, fishing is so stupid!
It satisfies your hunger! You
can't eat stones, that's for sure.
I see, you satisfy
your hunger by fighting?
Nobody can understand a
strong, high-spirited, solitary fighter.
Here, there is no fighting philosophy, no
spirit of victory, no formidable opponents!
I hate it, I hate this
countryside with nothing!
There is peace.
Peace...
Peace doesn't work for me.
This trembling fist,
burning passion and...
I will wilt without
using my incredible power...
He's so dark.
What?
Signal has changed?
I see.
Perhaps, because you
sneezed during the programming...
The Mira system must have a bug, and
interprets it as a command to transform.
So, Signal will
transform when I sneeze?
No, Nobuhiko!
Oh, it's the sea, it's the sea!
It's not the sea, it's a lake!
I see!
It's a lake with lots of sea!
No, Mini!
Chocolate!
H-He's getting eaten!
My name is Nobuhiko Otoi.
My parents went to study abroad...
...so I came to my grandpa's
house in the town of Dokari.
Okay, copying finished.
What about the plum colored one?
I was told to leave it as a souvenir.
Oh, Mr. Nobuhiko,
Signal, good morning!
Good morning.
Okay, let's get out of here.
Yep.
I'm home.
Chocolate!
Chocolate, chocolate!
I know, Mini!
What are we going to do, Bro?
What do you mean?
Chris, I'm hungry!
Got any snacks?
Chocolate, chocolate!
Is she in the lab?
Bro, wait up Bro...
I-It's okay, she's asleep.
She's not here.
Maybe she's in the study.
Alley-oop!
Hurry up, bro.
Stupid!
Let go of that branch!
Chris.
What is this run-down room?
Well, well.
I'm so disgusted
with your way of sleeping.
What?
You're kidding, this doesn't happen
no matter how much I toss and turn.
Then, who did this?
That's what I'd like to know.
Don't try to come up with some
poor excuse, help me clean a bit!
I'll pass!
You can't pass!
I'm a weak girl!
Physical labor is not good for me.
Come to think of it...
There was one girl who came to
me and wanted to be my apprentice.
She said that she would
do anything, even cleaning.
What was her name?
She was...
...a beautiful super-smart
girl, a super-smart beautiful girl...
I'm the one and only super
smart beautiful scientist, Chris Sine.
Then, take care of the cleaning!
Here, Sis.
Here.
Indeed, I have such a good apprentice.
What?
It's a fine day, isn't it?
How can a robot possibly tell the
difference between rainy and fine?
I feel all rusty when it is raining out.
Why don't you spray yourself
with some water-proof coating!
I' m going out for patrol!
I'll come along!
It's almost done.
Why didn't he let a
cleaning robot take care of it?
Other than Signal, I don't
know of any robots in this house.
Well, even if there was a robot
in this house, it wouldn't perfect.
The robot would be useless, and
wouldn't be able to do complicated tasks!
Then why don't you
make one by yourself?
What grandpa was saying reminded
me that you' re robot scientist yourself!
I don't want to see a small
project like a cleaning robot...
...so show me what you
mean by making a perfect robot!
Well, that's only if you could, you know.
Don't mock me!
I don't claim to be a
beautiful robot scientist for nothing!
When the right time comes,
when the right time comes...
When the right time comes, I will
make such a perfect super robot!
But...
...out of jealousy, the
professor told me not to use his lab!
He just hates my talent!
That must be it!
You're just saying that.
Just complaining?
Saying or
complaining, something like that.
It's even a fool knows Signal!
It's Signal to rescue the weak!
Yes, my name is Signal!
What the... what a messy room!
T-That... useless...
We've just cleaned up.
Grandpa, grandpa.
What?
Ms. Chris, good timing!
You didn't use the lab
on your own, did you?
No, I didn't.
Someone got the Mira data.
More importantly, look at this!
What about the album?
But, but, but...
How can you have such
an old picture of Signal?
Nobuhiko...
...don't you remember
your own father's face?
But, it looks so much different now!
Because that picture is
from more than 20 years ago.
A while ago, me and
Masanobu made a test robot together.
We designed its face after Masanobu's
to avoid the trouble of making a new one.
Then, Signal's face was
made based on the same model.
So, I was just made as rehash.
Only your face...
...your insides are built from
the state of the art Mira model.
Don't complain!
Professor, I want to see that robot!
Me too!
It's not here,
Masanobu took it with him.
Is that so.
My prototype model...
...that makes it like my older brother.
You will see him sometime.
His name is perhaps... yes, Pulse.
I think it's Pulse.
Yes...
Hello.
Ms. Elara.
Ms. Elara, you came to see me?
No way, she came to see me!
What?
Anyway, is the Professor in?
It's my maintenance day.
Rats.
Well then, I'll take you to the lab.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, that's not fair, Signal.
I have to start all over again.
This way...
Hey, Signal!
Excuse me, Ms. Elara, wait a minute!
What is it?
Help me with the cleaning!
I'm a fighting robot.
I'm not programmed to clean.
What are you talking about!
This mess is because of you!
Oh, what happened to this room?
It was Signal.
Oh, my god!
What is this messy room!
You'd better start cleaning!
You're bad, Chris!
I see.
I'll help you.
No, no!
I can't let you do such a thing.
Leave it to me!
But...
I'll be okay!
I may not look like
it, but I really am neat.
Right!
Let him take care of it!
I'll take you to the lab.
What?
Okay?
Yes, despite my looks, I love cleaning!
I see.
Then, please take care of it.
Let's go!
W-Well...
W-What is it?
Poor thing.
A boy having an adolescent moment...
Damn you, Chris!
Let's see how you handle cleaning!
I see.
Signal has a thing for Elara.
If you want to go use the
toilet, do so during this break.
It's peaceful.
That's a good thing.
Indeed, here in the town of
Dokari its peaceful with no crime at all.
That's a good thing.
But if it stays like this, there'll be no
chance for me to show off my true abilities.
Hey, are you listening?
Yeah?
That's why I hate robots!
I hate them!
Did you hear that?
That man down there is bored.
All right, let's have some fun!
Hello, Otoi Robot Lab.
Is this Nobuhiko?
Dad?
Have you been good?
I'm good!
You sound well yourself.
Well, things are fine.
Hey, how's Mom?
She's here.
Here, Minoru.
Hello, Nobuhiko?
Mom, are you well?
Sure, I'm fine, but aren't
you lonely away from us?
No problem!
Grandpa made me a robot...
Why am I doing this?
...just like a big brother.
What are you saying?
That sounds great!
Are you done?
Nobuhiko, how about my father?
He's in the middle of
doing maintenance on Elara.
Oh...
...he's done.
Who is it?
Somebody who rarely calls.
Hello.
It's been a while, father.
Masanobu?
That's right!
This is the first time
you called since you left.
They say that no news is good news.
That means there's something wrong?
What?
Signal!
What is wrong with you, officer Shinjo?
Why are you wearing
your summer clothing?
Shut up!
Where is Signal?
I'm here.
Signal, you bastard!
Signal, you're under arrest!
Give me a break!
Oh, my precious handcuffs!
What's going on!
Signal has been with me all day!
That's true.
You are so rude!
Shut up!
He's the one who
attacked me suddenly!
I'm positive!
I just got a quick glance,
but that figure, that style...
Who else could it have been?
No...
...it was probably not Signal!
Pulse was stolen from Masanobu!
I understand that a robot
was stolen from Professor Otoi...
...but why would a stolen
robot from overseas be in this town?
I' m not sure why.
Maybe the program had a bug.
Signal, where are you going?
Whatever the cause, we
better find the robot and bring it here!
And if it's really Pulse,
only I will be able to capture it.
If it gives you trouble,
don't treat it too roughly.
You and Pulse are
both my precious sons.
Not rough...
...all right, I'll try my best.
Hey Signal, do you really understand?
Hey, Bro!
Okay, let's get out of here.
Yep.
We'll do the research at our end.
Sorry for the trouble, but
please take care of the rest.
Hello, Otoi...
Oh, Dad again.
I forgot to tell you something.
Do you want to talk to grandpa?
Just give him my message.
Listen well, it's big news.
What's that?
A super high-tech blade and
a mini-laser is attached to Pulse?
But...
Masanobu!
How could you build such a thing?
What's the surprise?
Didn't you want a strong robot?
Pulse is really strong now!
How well I've learned from my Dad!
Don't you agree, Minoru?
Well, we're looking for it now.
When we find it, we will call you again.
Stupid!
Pulse is here already!
Pulse has already gotten here.
There's a kid with no common sense.
Hey!
What's wrong, grandpa?
How do you do?
I am Pulse.
You must be Signal.
Actually, I am Signal, but...
That's not me, that's a white birch!
Pulse is so near-sighted!
I'm not done
bragging about my abilities.
Are you ready, Signal?
That's a stone.
Damn!
That's a fish.
Isn't he your pal?
Forgive me, forgive me, Pulse!
I must have some old data on Pulse.
What's this floppy?
I don't remember this.
Now Pulse, the Professor
asked me to take you home.
Give up and come with me.
What are you doing?
Long time no see, Professor Otoi.
This must be Dr.
Umanokoji Hoshimaro.
Umenokoji Hoshimaro?
The robot called Pulse
which you created, is excellent.
Are you saying that you stole Pulse?
Yes, I hate you...
That's why I ordered Pulse to
destroy your precious Signal.
Why are you fighting with me?
We' re brothers!
We've no reason to fight!
I don't know!
Signal, The only thing l
know is that I must destroy you!
You stubborn...
No good!
Signal is in danger!
Isn't Pulse just a prototype of Signal?
So, isn't Signal technically better?
Only if Masanobu
hadn't changed anything!
At present, Pulse is a lethal weapon!
A walking knife!
Signal's materials can be torn by his
mono-molecular cutter or burnt by his laser!
I'll go and look for Signal!
Hey, Nobuhiko!
The robot you created will be
destroyed by another of your creations!
I wonder how that feels?
How could you do this!
This data will...
Self-destruct?
That's dangerous!
Too bad.
This data produces a
computer virus automatically.
I Look forward to seeing you again.
What have you done, Dr. Umanokoji?
Professor!
Hang in there!
Bring the Professor to his bed!
Right!
Well done.
You guys bring the data and
he brings the actual materials.
This is perfect.
Signal, Signal!
Where are you?
I suppose the time has come.
Signal, Signal!
The movement of the blade in his arm...
He's too strong!
Oh no!
Elara was kidnapped!
All right Epsilon, Gatling Punch!
That's not the enemy, Chris!
It's already too late to stop!
Signal!
Elara!
Next time on Twin Signal...
When a Family Game Runs Wild!
Quit sulking and do something, Chris!
What on Earth?