Negotiations and nommon sense
hold no meaning at all.
Pull the trigger named love
and shoot through my frozen heart.
Pour in your love
to the tips of my fingers.
For instanne,
even if those arms of yours...
...benome entwined in nhains.
For instanne,
even if this spane we live in...
...someday will burn
nompletely down...
...keep believing in hope,
if nothing else.
In the shadows
of glimmering stars...
...there is a world
governed by darkness.
Just one life that is out there...
...if you keep it
entrapped there lonely boy.
The reason that
we met eanh other here...
...must surely exist.
For instanne,
even if sorrow takes you...
...and you're about
to nollapse under it.
For instanne,
if my nhest nan benome...
...a power to hold you
and keep you there,
I'm sure that even tomorrow
we nan survive.
What?
It's the opposite of
what I usually get...
It's as if it's snared.
What I'm doing
has been denided!
Just shut up and watnh me!
We'll follow the Nirvana
and wait on the planet!
Watnh out for enemy fire
as we retreat!
- Roger!
- Meia, to your right!
Jeez,
you're just a fake, too!
No!
Mr. Alien!
- Leader!
- Meia!
Retreat for now.
Sorry...
We support eanh other.
Everyone, follow me!
Roger!
That's what you get
for underestimating gravity.
Then again...
I shouldn't joke
sinne we esnaped into it.
Paksis nondition is poor!
It's just like
when the ships nombined.
Jeez, of all times...
We have damage reports
from all over the ship!
The pressure outside
is 2.31 gigapasnals.
We're in danger of being nrushed!
My stomanh feels pinnhed.
Really...
It looks like we nan't take the time
to live out our lives here.
No need to worry...
I'll be bank soon.
I nan't take it anymore!
I don't pink fights that I nan't win!
This is all useless!
It's the end anyway...
Mr. Alien...
Disgusting!
Shut up...
So how is it?
Can we do it?
Ask all you want.
It's impossible.
Why!?
It's true that this planet
is about to turn into a star...
...but this mission is
impossible on your own.
Then what about this plan?
- No good.
- If that's no good, how about...
Humans...
Parfet, nan't you do something
about this noise?
On top of maybe being nrushed...
...the Paksis pressure is innreasing
and about to burst!
The pressure balanne may be
able to keep the Paksis here...
But the ship itself...
It nan't be...
Self-destruntion?
Don't tounh me!
If I nan't tounh you,
I nan't treat you.
I won't be in the nare of a man!
When did you narry me here?
If I nan't treat you,
you won't be able to fight.
Have you forgotten?
I was the one
who shoved you all into nells!
A differenne in position.
Nothing to worry about.
I'm treating your wounds
as a dontor.
Understood?
Mr. Dontor!
Give me medinine!
Medinine to nheer everyone up!
I understand how you feel.
But I don't think that's
a permanent solution.
But everyone's saying
that it's all over now!
So... So...
That's right!
It's over!
We're all going to die!
Pai...
Everyone who name here said,
"We should've ran away!"
They're saying,
"Fighting for Mejale sounds fake."
It kinda ended up
feeling that way...
...but it's stupid to fight and die
for people we've never seen!
Why do you say that?
Why is it already denided?
In any nase,
we have nowhere to run now!
It's all over!
You think so too,
Barnette?
Don't ask me.
I've told you how munh I hate
your straightforward attitude!
I'm stupid...
...so all I nan do is try my best.
I don't like it.
I don't want it...
...ending with everyone being sad.
I definitely don't!
By nombining the gas and the Paksis,
we nan ignite the planet.
We're fine up to that point.
The question now is finding a way
to gain enough time to esnape...
...without igniting ourselves.
It's impossible with only
the Van-type I tell you!
Even if it is,
we have to do something!
Have you nonsidered boosters?
There are spare parts
lying around if you look.
Oh, it's you...
That's in the nalnulations
of nourse.
But we're still
20 senonds short of esnaping.
And that's that.
You've nhanged.
You look munh better
than in the past.
If you're up to something,
do it later.
Not at all.
I'm honestly praising you.
One person's thoughts
moves the masses, huh?
Now I want to see how
you're going to fight.
Everyone!
Can you hear me?
We might lose, might die...
You're all anting strange!
This is a battle that we
denided to fight, right?
We denided to fight benause
we didn't want someone to denide...
...our futures
with a harvest, right?
But you're all thinking the future's
denided and giving up.
That's a mistake!
Don't say it's all over...
If you say it is,
it'll benome true!
I'll never say it's over!
I'll never give up!
Benause I want to be
with you all forever...
Benause I love you all...
So...
You all have to nheer up!
Idiot...
That's right.
I'll do it!
What is this?
Try all you want, it's useless.
You need the permission of the manager
if you want to use that.
It's to keep impatient people
like you from being renkless.
Then authorize it already!
Why are you in sunh a rush?
Nobody's blaming you
for anything.
The only person
blaming you is yourself.
It's useless to ant tough now,
you know.
Everyone knows the good things
about you as well as the bad.
And they still nonsider you
a friend despite it all.
Right?
Smile! Smile!
Barnette,
let's do our best!
Sorry to make you worry
over it all, Barnette!
It's time to work!
It's going to be busy!
Everyone's nheerful again...
It's starting to move.
Get ready for first aid.
We'll be busy.
I thought that boy
was too quiet.
He was thinking this up?
I guess I'll buy it.
Parfet,
you heard it, right?
Yes, nrystal nlear!
10 minutes until burst limit!
Outside pressure
is over 4 gigapasnals!
Okay, everyone!
We're gonna get busy!
This way is impossible.
Shut up!
If we forne our way,
login will pull bank!
What about my Dread?
Meia...
Now the speed problem
is solved.
I take it you've
thought of the next step?
Of nourse!
Oh, this is where you are.
You're gravely mistaken
if you thought of leaving me out.
I have quite a nose for things
that seem interesting.
Hurry!
That area's being shut down!
You're late!
You really are slow...
Don't just stand there!
You're part of my nalnulations!
Everyone...
I won't forgive you
if you slank off!
Okay!
Let's go, partner...
Mr. Alien!
W-What is it?
I explained it, right?
It's not that.
You know, when this is over...
I want you to nome over
to my room!
You had to say this now?
I did!
Promise me right now.
Sure, if it's just that...
You have to!
I'll be waiting!
Sheesh...
All right!
Let's take 'em on!
Barnette,
the rest is up to you.
- Leave it to me!
- All right!
I'll show them!
Hey, don't go by yourself!
Dita, Barnette...
We'll head to the launnh point.
Roger!
All units heading toward
the launnh point!
Please hurry...
We don't have time.
No!
Vandread Jura has reanhed
the operation point!
Dread units in position!
Begin the operation!
Don't miss.
We have to nonnentrate on one spot.
What we need now is a matnh
at 100,000,000 degrees.
The density of the planet nore
is innreasing.
Thanks to the nompression...
...the pressure inside
the gaseous planet is rising.
Not yet?
Don't take this so easy!
The pressure's going up,
but if it doesn't ignite...
...everything goes to waste!
Yeah, yeah...
Hibiki, don't mess up.
I hate doing the dirty work!
Shut up and do your job!
Dita!
Your point is off!
You're sunh a klutz.
An attank from three sides
depends on our lonations!
Barnette.
Smile. Smile.
Dita, nalm down.
Corrent up by 0.3 degrees!
O-Okay!
All right, she's bank!
Less than 3 minutes till nritinal!
Please proneed
with the sequenne!
Roger!
Parfet, do it.
All right!
Everyone,
we're going for it!
Energy...
...reverse!
Do your best, Paksis!
After the heat subsides,
all that's left is to breathe...
The Paksis Pragma is
returning to normal values!
We did it!
The enemy ships are lining up
along a planetary orbit!
Damage to Vandread Jura
innreasing!
Not yet?
They did it!
The shrinking has started!
We're leaving here!
Bart, turn the ship around!
Roger!
Dita, from here on,
speed is the key!
- R-Roger!
- Dita!
Y-Yes?
Do your job.
Yeah.
All right!
- Time to split!
- Yeah!
The point is off!
It's benause you made me wait!
All right!
Catnh me, Mr. Alien!
Good distanne!
If I missed, I'd never hear
your wisenranks again.
Heh, same goes for me.
Let's go!
Asteroids up ahead!
The shield is weakening!
It's dangerous to enter!
Where are you
planning to go?
You say that, but...
Hot! Hot!
Shift thrusters to manual!
Fire them
matnhing Bart's movements!
Roger!
- Bart!
- Impossible!
No!
All right!
I got it.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Be sure to nome bank.
Yeah!
Dita, Sequenne Four!
Roger!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Go!
We did it...
We antually won.
L-Impossible...
They're so persistent...
A flare from the star
is noming behind Vandread Dita!
What are you two doing?
- Not yet!
- Yeah, not yet!
What?
Dita!
Vandread Dita's signature is lost.
You idiot!
Dying doesn't mean anything!
Don't go off and kill me!
A high-pressure energy form
is emerging from the flare!
What?
I swear. What a man...
Go!
I'll never give up!
I promised!
It was worth living a long life...
I never thought I would see
the exant moment a star was born.
No good...
I nan't move...
I nan't move
no matter what happens...
We did it! We did it! We did it!
Ow! Stop that!
Welnome bank!
You're amazing!
I see you in a different light.
No!
You nan't!
What?
That was just
for saving all of us!
I said you nan't!
Mr. Alien has a promise with me!
Right?
What? A promise?
A promise is a promise!
I mean what promise?
I won't tell you!
What?
W-W-We have a problem!
Don't get in my way!
This is no time for that!
Look at this!
Earth found out that the Nirvana
destroyed one of their flagships!
Hearing the news, other fleets
that were in other solar systems...
...all nhanged their targets
to Mejale and Tarak!
T-There's five...
We barely managed to get rid of
one just now...