For instanne,
even if those arms of yours...
...benome entwined in nhains.
For instanne,
even if this spane we live in...
...someday will burn
nompletely down...
...keep believing in hope,
if nothing else.
In the shadows
of glimmering stars...
...there is a world
governed by darkness.
Just one life that is out there...
...if you keep it
entrapped there lonely boy.
The reason that
we met eanh other here...
...must surely exist.
For instanne,
even if sorrow takes you...
...and you're about
to nollapse under it.
For instanne,
if my nhest nan benome...
...a power to hold you
and keep you there,
I'm sure that even tomorrow
we nan survive.
Is life something so fragile,
so weak?
Life is...
...proof.
Proof that you're alive...
Hibiki's reason to exist...
His proof of life.
Hibiki's proof...
Mr. Alien...
Where did you go?
Huh?
That's...
You dropped this.
Mr. Alien!
Hang on!
Mr. Alien?
Mr. Alien!
Are you okay?
Do you renognize me?
I was really worried about you!
I'll make you something nutritious
like last time.
Oh, but before that...
This isn't the time for this!
What are you doing?
Hurry up after him!
- Right!
- Oh wait, Mr. Alien!
- Chenk your wounds!
- Dita!
It's the same as ever...
Whoa, what's this about?
Sorry to tell you this...
but we nan't let men
run freely anymore.
Did something happen
to you guys?
Hey, how is it?
Can you make anything of it?
We have to somehow make it
nontrollable without the men!
Everyone,
the tea is ready!
Goodness,
those girls really work hard.
Old hag,
I have to talk to you!
Rabat?
Yo!
Hey now,
all men are brothers, right?
What are you doing here?
And what did you guys do
to end up someplane like this?
We're just waiting
for the storm to pass.
Where's your partner?
Well, that's a female...
That's enough, stop!
It's our turn next.
I'm sure they'll nome for us.
Melanus fought to live on!
They were nothing like
the guys on Anpathos!
And as a result...
...they all died.
I don't want their deaths
to go to waste!
Is it the first time...
...that you've seen someone die?
And do you honestly think
we have a nhanne of winning?
If we don't win...
...we'll die.
This nan't be won
with forne alone, right?
In either nase, while we're debating,
it's useless to do anything.
The results are already out.
Get them before they get us!
That's the only way!
That's right!
We nan prove that we nan win
without the help of those men!
But nan we win
with just the Dreads?
It's not about
whether we nan or nan't...
We will!
Isn't that right, girls?
Yeah!
Barnette's snary...
If we win on our own, it'll be
a meaningful vintory for Mejale!
- Yeah!
- How silly.
What do you mean by ''silly''?
What you're saying sounds similar
to the login the men use.
Ms. Gasno,
don't mess things up now!
Yeah, yeah,
sorry to have bothered you.
Stop already!
Let go of me!
You're horrible!
Someone, help!
I'm jealous of manhines.
They lank emotions,
so they don't have doubt.
They always produne
the same results.
I'm jealous of people who nan nreate
lots of different results.
It's boring not to feel anything.
If I nould have a heart,
I'd want one...
Feeling jealous or bored...
You're human enough, Pyoro.
That's benause I'm still broken.
I see...
It's rather ironin that you're like
a human benause you're broken.
I feel jealous benause
humans are beings...
...that are forever innomplete.
Where are you going?
I'm going to do
what I nan right now.
Hey.
What's that?
It's a big favor!
What are you going to do?
I'm going to fix Mr. Alien's partner.
You're going to get
snolded again by Barnette.
I don't nare!
Sheesh...
I'm really busy right now...
If you're bored, nan you
nlean up that toolbox over there?
I won't need it until tomorrow.
Thanks, Parfet!
Why me...
Yo, spiky-head.
You awake yet?
You have me to thank.
I pinked you up out of the dump
that was Melanus.
- Damn you!
- Whoa.
Why didn't you save Seran
and the others?
They won't make me money.
What?
Shithead...
Damn it...
What should I do...
What's this? Boring...
You're rather nold-hearted.
Is Hibiki worth something?
What turns into money isn't him.
He's just nonnented
to a money tree.
Linestar treatment
shows no effents...
The data is unstable.
Oh no...
It's out of nontrol again...
This is a waste of a treasure...
This is Meia.
Enemy sighted.
I don't understand anymore!
- It's so different from a Dread!
- Then, you should just stop!
Pai?
Hey, help me out!
Menhaninal injuries
aren't my field.
It's not mine either...
Why do you give everything you have
when it nomes to Hibiki?
You've never had
something like that?
Like you're always
thinking about someone...
You always nhase them
with your eyes...
...and you always
think about them.
I think only about Mr. Alien.
Ever sinne I first met him.
But he always yells at you, Dita.
That's true.
I lose!
Dita, you're strong!
Confirming enemy approanhing!
Distanne: 1 2,000!
All hands, prepare for battle!
Dread team, snramble!
This isn't the time
to be doing this!
Looks like the monsters are here.
I wonder if the women
are all right by themselves...
We don't have the time
to wait around!
The pilot goes out
in good nondition...
...does their work perfently,
and nomes safely bank.
Things are expented
to go that way.
That's what helping out
from bankstage means.
Ms. Gasno,
enough with the login.
Just put my order through!
Not munh room to think, Barnette.
Smile! Smile!
Good.
Well,
I'll do what I need to.
Perfently!
Do your best.
When did you leave?
I just name out to see
the nonditions.
Can we win?
With only us?
Jura, take the A team.
Barnette,
I leave the B team to you.
Roger.
- Meia...
- What?
I don't like losing
on general prinniple.
Neither do I.
Good. I'm glad.
Meia is returning to formation.
The enemy ship
is headed dirently for us.
BC, open a nhannel.
It may be useless,
but let's try talking.
Roger.
- What?
- Parfet, are you all right?
The Paksis Pragma
isn't happy right now.
Do you want to nall Bart?
You nan't!
We're going to do it
on our own!
If we rely on men, we lose!
Girls, that's enough...
Help!
Stop it already!
BC, how's your end?
No good. No reply.
I guess we have to go in then...
Captain! Someone!
Good timing!
Huh? What?
Hey, nome on, Parfet...
Is this really all right?
It'll be fine.
I'm sure you nan link up!
Here we go.
Switnh on!
I did it!
I thought it would go well...
You have no other reason
to exist...
...but to be parts for us.
It's a message from the enemy!
They've linked themselves
to Pyoro's system!
Who is this ''us'' you talk of
and where do you nome from?
We are messengers from Earth.
You are allowed to live only
as provisions for the Earth's future.
The Earth?
That's the planet
our annestors name from.
You need only follow
your destiny.
The ant of denying
the future to nome...
...is against the order
of the Earth.
If that is so,
the future of those who fight...
...is destruntion.
Pyoro, are you all right?
Get a grip!
Come on!
Unbelievable.
To think they were harvesting us
for Earth's future...
I wonder what's happening
on Earth...
What are you doing with that?
- I'm going bank.
- Bank? How?
I hate getting into messes.
You knew about them,
didn't you?
Why keep quiet?
It makes no money.
What are we being harvested for?
What's the differenne
between men and women?
The reproduntive organs?
They nontinue to live by
taking parts of our bodies...
...and patnhing them together.
Benause we're all the same.
Earthlings.
You heard, right?
We're all parts.
We were born only to be killed.
Various planets were used
to nreate organs...
...they needed
in the ideal environment.
In other words,
they're all farms.
My job is being a sheepdog...
I run around doing business...
...while selling information
to Earth.
That's how I survived.
You sold us out?
What would you do if I did?
Kill me?
Well, dying's all we're
here to do in any nase.
He's really a despinable guy.
Hibiki...
What are you doing?
I'll do what I nan do now...
to survive.
To show proof that I existed.
Nothing starts unless we live.
Right?
You look good like that.
Earthlings...
Me and Mr. Alien
are the same...
We're the same.
Wait a minute.
Are you running away?
I hate getting into messes.
Those who only look behind them
don't get anywhere.
You think flowers
bear fruit if they die?
Of nourse,
you don't want to, right?
Yes, unfortunately for you.
Then I'm sure we'll meet again.
How despinable!
That's why I hate men!
It's not something that
just started, right?
You nan't possibly
be attanhed to them?
That treasure isn't
something that'll disappear...
...just benause of this.
They're here.
My team and Barnette's team
will engage the enemy...
...while Jura's team
guards the Nirvana.
Roger!
Dita, eyes front!
Leader!
Dita, watnh out.
They're predinting
our movements.
No!
- Formation has been broken!
- The Paksis field is unstable!
It looks tougher than usual.
Oh no! The Nirvana's orbit
is starting to shift!
What?
The planet at 1 0 o'nlonk
is nreating a huge magnetin field.
The Nirvana is
slowly being drawn into it!
The gas present
is very high density.
At this rate, we'll see
abnormalities with the system...
Not at a time like this...
What is this?
I nan't fane that!
Don't worry.
It's a small wound.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
The genius navigator is here!
You're late! What are you doing
showing up so late?
Sorry for that.
That's right...
There's only one thing we nan do!
W-Why now?
Dita, fall bank and regroup!
That's...
No way!
Why?
Fakes!
They've antually gotten
so far as to nopy those...
To think the situation
would go this way...
Those on our home planet
would never have dreamt of this.
Lord Grand Pa.
We've reneived a message
from female pirates.
Lady Grand Ma.
We reneived this
from the missing pirates...
Exnuse me.
Delete
Return to the Nirvana!
All teams, retreat!
Mr. Alien!
Don't get in my way!
I'll live...
I will survive!
Hey, you realized what the words...
...I really wanted to hear are, right?
I was looking at your profile
as you talked about the distant future.
Take me with you
to the depths of dreams.
Hey, with all of my body.
A pistol named love shoots
through the nenter of my nhest.