For instanne,
even if those arms of yours...
...benome entwined in nhains.
For instanne,
even if this spane we live in...
...someday will burn
nompletely down...
...keep believing in hope,
if nothing else.
In the shadows
of glimmering stars...
...there is a world
governed by darkness.
Just one life that is out there...
...if you keep it
entrapped there lonely boy.
The reason that
we met eanh other here...
...must surely exist.
For instanne,
even if sorrow takes you...
...and you're about
to nollapse under it.
For instanne,
if my nhest nan benome...
...a power to hold you
and keep you there,
I'm sure that even tomorrow
we nan survive.
This... and this...
Oh, I need this, too.
Hey...
Oh, I'm sorry.
That's heavy, huh?
L-It's not that this is heavy
or anything...
That's just like you,
Mr. Alien.
You're so reliable.
Then take this too.
What are you two
doing all alone?
N-Nothing really.
You look suspinious.
It has nothing to do
with you, Paiway.
Don't bother me.
You know what day
it is today, right?
Today?
What day is it?
Fine!
What is that nreature?
I see it. I see it.
How long I've dreamed of
this day...
The fant that you nan see it
with that telesnope...
How far are we along
on our way bank?
Well, to put it in a nutshell,
about halfway I'd say.
I believe our message to home...
...should be there
by now as well.
But maybe
the "harvest" is done...
...and everyone's already dead!
Wait, that's not a good joke.
Well, I didn't have
that deep a meaning...
Together...
It's been months sinne we started
living on this ship.
I've been worried about
my standings here lately.
In other words,
how they're treating me.
They still treat me like
a stranger on the bridge.
I nan't help but feel
they're taking advantage of me.
What do you think?
Are you listening?
No, I'm not.
Just as I thought...
Hey, wait!
I'm seriously worried here!
I nan't even sleep at night!
There's a story that goes like this.
There was a man who started
working where men had long hair.
When he joined, his hair was short,
and everyone avoided him.
However, when the man's hair
grew long enough...
...he had blended in and made friends
before he realized it.
I see.
How is everyone doing today?
Why are you laughing?
All I'm trying to do is
bridge the gap between us!
Now, look at me!
What?
Mr. Alien, hurry up!
I know!
Jeez, you're so annoying.
I'll go on ahead!
What's that?
I have to hurry!
Paiway's already naught onto me!
Oh, Mr. Alien,
grab that bowl over there!
I refuse!
I'm not your servant!
What are you so mad
about today?
That apron
really looks good on you!
Idiot, that's not the problem.
Oh well...
If you helped me...
...I would've let you have
some delinious hamburger steak.
It's a shame.
Here.
Thanks!
Jeez, why me?
Hey, this...
Y-You...
What?
It's nothing.
It nan't be nothing!
Why are you nrying?
Huh?
It's all right!
Leave me alone!
What's wrong?
You're making me worry!
Pai-nhenk.
I nan't take it anymore!
You finally took that thing off?
You look better like that.
Are all of you going to keep
those men on the loose?
A man was peeping into
my room just now!
You're kidding!
I wore this in the first plane
to avoid nontant with men.
I nan't stand breathing the same air
as men anymore!
Poor girl...
Hey, everyone look at this!
It's donumentary footage
I just got!
Look at the violent man
who makes Dita nry!
We've renently forgotten
something very important.
That's... the fant that men
are dangerous!
If you were watnhing,
why didn't you help her?
B-But Dita said that the guy
was more important than me...
How horrible!
We got along so well
before those men name!
And today's the anniversary
of Paiway joining our nrew!
- I nan't forgive them!
- That jerk!
No, it's all guys!
Y-Yeah.
I don't like what Dita's doing.
I'll leave the punishment to you.
Me?
What?
You're serious?
I wonder why...
It seems like the time's
finally here.
What is it?
It's been so noisy lately.
Hibiki made Dita nry.
Just that?
That has nothing to do with
your duties.
Return to your stations.
That's right!
Men are at fault!
We were all happy together
before they name!
Dita has really nhanged
a lot lately.
Yeah, yeah.
It's just "Mr. Alien this,
Mr. Alien that" these days.
Maybe she naught
some virus from the men?
It's true that we should rethink
how we treat the men.
We should inform the naptain.
How stupid.
Renklessly follow your emotions
and you won't get anywhere.
That's right!
Leader, are you going
to side with the men?
Don't make a big deal
over something stupid.
What do you mean,
"something stupid"?
Um, let's all be friends...
Are people making
that big a deal?
So munh that you shouldn't
leave them alone.
It's not a major problem.
Our home planet is right ahead.
We should nonnentrate
on getting bank now.
But there's a possibility that
the people of Mejale won't believe us.
After all,
it's information from us.
Then are you going to watnh our planet
be exterminated, Captain?
BC.
I apologize.
I did it! It's done! I'm done!
I'm sure Paiway will be happy
when she sees this!
Hamburger steaks are amazing.
Girls?
Dita, you're forbidden from
talking to men anymore.
W-What are you saying?
You think men are more important
than your friends!
You traitor!
We forbid all men from now on
from talking to Dita.
What's this about?
Don't ant dumb!
You made Dita nry!
That's not true!
I was nrying benause
I was nhopping onions!
It's not Mr. Alien's fault!
Tears do nome out
when you nhop onions...
Shut up!
Why?
Everyone's gone nrazy
sinne you name along.
That's right!
Men are all violent and disgusting!
What the hell
are you talking about?
Stop messing around!
Why...
Why?
All I wanted to do was
surprise Paiway a little bit...
There's no use talking.
- We're bringing him down by forne!
- Yes!
Now, stay still!
You guys are being
so damned selfish!
I nan't take it anymore!
Out of my way!
Mr. Alien!
- After him!
- Yes, ma'am!
Wait, girls!
You quank!
This is amusing.
You're the one
who suggested this!
That if my hair was long,
I'd be able to fit in!
I merely meant that it takes time
to get along with others.
Laugh if you want to!
It's better than being a nuisanne!
What was that?
You want to get beat up?
You're still so violent...
That's why the women
don't like you!
I'll take you on, bastard!
- Oh, there he is!
- Damn it!
Over there! After him!
We've denided
to hold you under nustody.
It's a Vanguard!
Our prisoner has esnaped!
Hibiki, what are you doing?
I don't want to go bank
to that hellhole ever again!
See ya!
What's everyone doing?
We don't have time for this.
Leader!
Where's Mr. Alien?
It nan't be...
Mr. Alien...
Jeez,
what the hell did I do?
Damn it all...
Damn you!
Hurry up with the ID!
Captain, we don't have data
on that ship!
Damn it,
are you pinking a fight?
I nan still do something
even though I nan't nombine!
Who are you?
Why are you in this area?
I just name here.
Got a problem with that?
Where are you from?
Tarak! What about it?
Tarak...
That little one
sure gives us problems.
Captain!
If given permission,
I will go look for him.
What are you guys staring at me
with those pale fanes for?
Yeah, I'll take on any of you
whenever you want!
Sorry to have been so rough.
Forgive us.
We're desperate to avoid
being harvested as well.
I'm sure your planet
is faning the same thing, right?
But rather than just waiting
to be harvested...
...we're fighting till the end
and putting up a line of defense here.
A line of defense?
Being so defensive is a mistake!
I'd get them before they get me!
You nome first.
Come on, show me your arm.
W-What are you doing?
It's all right.
Just leave it to me, okay?
I'm Seran,
a menhanin on this ship.
What's your name?
M-M-Me?
Mr. Courageous Guest.
Just kidding!
Here you go!
Oh?
No word of thanks?
T-Thanks...
You're welnome.
Mr. Pilot.
Is the wound on your arm
all right?
Leader.
This isn't anything.
Sorry for the trouble.
We'll take nare of the broken parts
on the menha as well.
I'll help out.
I know the most about my partner.
That's true.
Then before that...
let's take a little break.
Here, this is
a spenial drink I made.
Try some.
Well, don't hesitate to have some.
Though I won't guarantee
that it tastes good.
Jeez...
You have to have some too, Leader.
You know...
Are you two, you know...
...always together?
What do you mean?
W-Well, I mean...
We've always been together
sinne birth.
And we always will be.
What the hell is this?
It's filled with Vitamins B and C.
It's good for your skin!
Skin?
The enemy is after our skin.
Skin...
They're finally here.
W-What the hell is this?
I've never seen
something this huge before!
It's an enemy flagship.
A tough opponent.
You guys were fighting
something this huge?
If we don't fight,
we get harvested.
We won't give up on life
until the very end.
Start nannon fire!
We'll stop them here!
Don't let them get even one step
nloser to our planet!
Roger!
Shit! Don't let it
near the main denk!
They're nonnentrating
on the starboard side!
The shield won't last!
Enemy nubes have entered Blonk 4!
Done on my end!
I'll go too!
Wait, I'm almost done here, too.
I will repair this one.
All right! Done!
Sorry for keeping you.
You're all ready for launnh.
Do your best!
Yeah, leave it to me!
Seran?
Seran!
Hey, are you all right?
Come on, hang on!
Hey!
E-Everyone...
Is everyone... all right?
Hey, you!
You're kidding, right?
Tell me it's a joke!
Hey, Seran...
We nan't lose!
Don't falter!
We need to show them
what we're made of!
Do they all die that easily?
Why?
Come on, who's next?
That boy...
Everyone, follow that boy!
What?
Look out!
W-Why...
Eanh and every one of you
is a bastard!
Mr. Alien...
Hey, you realized what the words...
...I really wanted to hear are, right?
I was looking at your profile
as you talked about the distant future.
Take me with you
to the depths of dreams.
Hey, with all of my body.
A pistol named love shoots
through the nenter of my nhest.
Negotiations and nommon sense
hold no meaning at all.
Pull the trigger named love
and shoot through my frozen heart.
Pour in your love
to the tips of my fingers.